Finding Aid for the Dr. Ingram Bloch Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Dr. Ingram Bloch Collection
Undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0045
.42 linear_feet
Biographical Sketch
Dr. Ingram Bloch, 1920-1995 was a Physics professor at Vanderbilt University starting in 1948 until his passing in 1995. He was the son of Oscar Edgeworth Bloch, Sr. and Katherine Ingram Bloch. He was a fan of the theater and collected playbills from events he attended.
Scope and Content Note
The Ingram Bloch Collection is an archive of old playbills and programs spanning from 1929 to 1953. The collection arranges items chronologically, starting with 1929 and ending with 1953 and unknown dates. The collection primarily features theater programs, along with some opera programs. Some publications in the collection include: Chicago Stagebill, The Playgoer, The Playbill of Chicago Theaters, Goodman Theatre, Harris Theater, and others.
- Box Listing
  - Playbills—Programs, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Playbills—Programs, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Playbills—Programs Unknown date (Box 1, Folder 25)